Guide to the Speeches and Articles by and about Presidents of Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Speeches and articles concerning A. Bartlett Giamatti, 1960-1987; Accession 1988-A-054
  - Journal-Courier: "Giamatti Named NL Proxy, Will Remain Fan of Red Sox, 1986 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - Journal-Courier: "Bart is a Good Choice but Irwin Deserved It", 1986 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Journal-Courier: "Views Differ on Giamatti's Appointment", 1986 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - Hartford Courant: "Yale President Leaving Ivy League Behind for Astroturf", 1986 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Hartford Courant: "Giamatti, a Man of Letters, Calls DH 'Appalling'", 1986 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 279)
  - Journal-Courier: "Darling Backs Bart", 1986 June 12 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Journal-Courier: "Giamatti's Surprise Switch", 1986 June 13 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Hartford Courant: "Batting Bart", 1986 June 13 (Box 11, Folder 282)
  - The New York Times "Leading the League", 1986 June 15 (Box 11, Folder 283)
  - Yale Weekly Bulletin and Calendar: ABG Pix, 1986 June 16-30 (Box 11, Folder 284)
  - Newsweek: "Ivy Switch", 1986 June 23 (Box 11, Folder 285)
  - Time: "In a Green Field, In the Sun", 1986 June 23 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - The New Haven Register: "Solvancy is Giamatti's Legacy to Yale", 1986 June 29 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - The Washington Post - "Style" section: "Giamatti: to the Fields of Heaven", 1986 July 2 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - The Boston Globe: "A Chat with the President", 1986 August 6 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Drafts, 1985-1886 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - A Developmental Perspective (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Information gathered for articles on President Giamatti - outlining his presidency, undated (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Alumni Events, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Political Possibilities, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - New Haven Register: Sports, 1987 March 3 (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - General Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 297-300)
  - ABG & Walter D. Littell Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 301)
  - ABG & WDL Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 302)
  - Requests - Speeches/Articles, 1978-1979, 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 303-307)
  - Permission Granted: ABG Texts/Excerpts, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 308)
  - Town-Gown Relations - The New Haven Advocate AN EDUCATION FOR FREEDOM, Undated,1986 (Box 12, Folder 309-310)
  - Yale Law School Alumni Luncheon, 1980 October 25 (Box 13, Folder 311)
  - New England Association of Schools & Colleges, 1980 December 4 (Box 13, Folder 312)
  - Yale Club of Southern California (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Anti-Defamation League Dinner, 1982 April 25 (Box 13, Folder 314)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith: New England Regional Office, 1982 November 7 (Box 13, Folder 315)
  - AYA Assembly XXII: Humanities at Yale, 1983 April 14 (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1983 September 28 (Box 13, Folder 317)
  - AYA Assembly XXIII: Residential Colleges, 1983 October 20 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Young President's Organization, 1984 April 9 (Box 13, Folder 319)
- Articles and information concerning Kingman Brewster, 1941-1981; Accession 1988-A-056
  Scope and Contents
  The following articles were discarded because of mold:
  Bridgeport Sunday Post, pps. 1-2 --- 1964 Apr 5
  Hartford Courant --- 1965 Feb 6
  Yale Daily News --- 1964 Apr 10
  Yale Daily News --- 1963 Oct 14
  Yale Daily News --- 1964 Apr 8
  New Haven Register, "Features" Section, pg. 1 --- 1967 Jul 23
  New York Times Magazine, article by Andrew Hacker --- 1963
  Yale Daily News --- 1963 Apr 30
  Timothy Dwight College "Town Crier" --- 1961 Nov 21
  Day (?) New London, CT, Andrew Tully Column --- 1966 Sep 12
  Telegram (?) Bridgeport, CT, Andrew Tully Column --- 1966 Sep 12
  Yale Daily News, Summer Issue --- 1965
  Yale Daily News --- 1965 May 8
  Yale Daily News --- 1967 Nov 13
  Yale Daily News, "Friday" --- 1967 Dec 1
  Yale Daily News --- 1966 Sep 26
  New York Times, pg. 51 --- 1967 Feb 20
  Yale News and Review, Pg. 10 --- 1963 May 11
  Yale Daily News --- 1963 Sep 20
  Yale Daily News --- 1963 Sep 19
  Yale University News Bureau, Press Relaese #135 --- 1963 Nov 22
  New Haven Journal-Courier, pg. 22 --- 1964 Jan 2
  Yale News and Review --- 1964 Jan 18
  Yale News and Review --- 1964 Apr 11
  Saturday Review, pg. 28 --- 1965 Dec 11
  - Correspondence: Provost Brewster, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SPEECHES
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1963, 1963 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ARTICLES
    - Articles, Clippings; Brewster's Inauguration as President, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SPEECHES
    - Alumni Reunions, 1963 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Freshman Address; Class of 1967, 1963 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, Convocation, 1963 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ARTICLES
    - The Yale Daily News, 1963 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Yale News and Review, 1963 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, Cover Story, 1963 November (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SPEECHES
    - Butler University, 1964 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Yale Club of Cincinnati, 110th Anniversary, 1964February 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Yale Alumni Day, 1964 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - National Yale Alumni Meeting, Dallas Texas, 1964March 21 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Inaugural Address, 1964 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - OTHER
    - Press Kit, Inauguration of Kingman Brewster, Jr., 1964 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ARTICLES
    - Yale Alumni Magazine: Inauguration Issue, 1964 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - SPEECHES
    - Testimony: Subcommittee on Science, Research, and Development of the Committee on Science & Astrnautics, U.S. House of Representatives, Washington, D.C., 1964 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1964, 1964 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1968, 1964 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - United Fund of New Haven (United Way), 1964 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - The Hartford Courant, 200th Anniversary, 1964 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ARTICLES
    - Newsweek Magazine, Cover Story, 1964 November 23 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SPEECHES
    - New England Associations of Colleges and Schools, 1964 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, 75th Anniversary, 1965 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Recording for the Blind, Inc., Dedication, 1965 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Meeting, San Francisco, 1965 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - St. Lawrence University, Commencement Address, 1965June 6 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1965, 1965 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1969, 1965 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Williams College Fall Convocation, 1965 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - American Council on Education, 1965 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Washington, D.C. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Alumni, Yale Club of Southern California, 1965 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ARTICLES
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, By Kingman Brewster, Jr., 1965 December (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Alumni Day, 1966 February (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Connecticut College Commencement, 1966 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1966, 1966 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 265th commencement (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1970, 1966 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce, 1966 October 4 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - CFAE Detroit Luncheon Meeting, 1967 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article: The New York Times Sunday Magazine, 1967 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - SPEECHES
    - Alumni Day, 1967 February 18 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - National Association of Independent Schools, 1967March 3 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Camp Memorial Lectures "The Academic, 1967 May 7, 9, 11 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Process" Lectures I, II, III (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Baccalaureate Address, class of 1967, 1967 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - ARTICLES
    - Time Magazine Cover Story, 1967 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - SPEECHES
    - Parents Day 1967, 1967 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - OTHER
    - Confidential, Brewster, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - SPEECHES
    - University of Illinois Centennial Program, 1968 March 6 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - University of Illinois, 1968 March 6 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - George Wahington University Commencement, 1968 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1972, 1968 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - National Commission of the Causes and Prevention of Violence, 1968 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Capital for International Educational Development, 1969 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Yale Alumni Club of Philadelphia, 1969 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Institute of International Education Sixth Conference, 1969 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Special Report to Alumni, Alumni Day Luncheon, 1969February 22 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Economic Club of Chicago, 1969 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Johns Hopkins University Commencement, 1969 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1969, 1969 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1973, 1969 September 15 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - ARTICLES
    - Yale Political Union, By K.B., Jr., 1969 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report, 1969 October 7 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - SPEECHES
    - Vietnam Moratorim Meeting, 1969 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1969 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Michigan State University Commencement Exercises, 1969 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, Sigma Xi Lecture, 1969 December 29 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Clark University, Founders' Day Assembly, 1970 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - American Newspaper Publishers' Association, 1970April 21 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article - New York Times, 1970 April 30 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Baccalaureate Adress, Class of 1970, 1970 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Carleton College Commencement Address, 1970 June 11 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - ARTICLES
    - Newsweek Magazine Cover Story, 1970 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - SPEECHES
    - Annual Meeting, Luncheon, 1970 August 9 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1974, 1970 September 14 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - National Conference of Editors and Publishers, 1970October 12 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1970 November 10 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Ford Hall Forum: "The Deeper Unrest", 1970 December 6 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Stamford Forum, 1971 January 24 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Alumni Day Luncheon, 1971 February 20 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Bryn Mawr, 1971 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Remarks at Kent State University, 1971 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - University of Connecticut: Charge to the Graduates, 1971 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1971, 1971 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Reflections on our National Purpose, 1971 December 27 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report of the President, 1972 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - SPEECHES
    - Duke University, 1972 February 16 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - President's Lecture Series, Rice University, 1972April 20 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Notre Dame University, Commencement Address, 1972May 21 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report of President 1971-1972, 1972 August 28 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - SPEECHES
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1976, 1972 September 11 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report, 1971-1972 Academic Tenure, 1972 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - SPEECHES
    - Alumni Day, 1973 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 50th Anniversary, Belmont Hill School, 1973 May 19 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1973, 1973 June 3 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report of the President, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - SPEECHES
    - College and University Business Officers, 1973 July 9 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article - New York Times, by K. Brewster, 1973 September 6 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - SPEECHES
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1973, 1973 September 3 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article - House and Garden Magazine, by K.B.,Jr., 1973 October (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Article - Yale Daily News, 1973 October 12 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - SPEECHES
    - Yale Assemble Convocation Dinner, 1973 October 26 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Commercial Club, 1973 December 18 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Alumni Day, 1974 March 2 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Yale Club of Washington, D.C. 100th Anniversary, 1974 March 6 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - OTHER
    - Interview on "Speaking Freely" with Edwin Newman, 1974 March 29 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - SPEECHES
    - Capital Campaign Announcement, 1974 April 8 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1974April 25 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1974, 1974 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Chautauqua Centennial, 1974 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Comments on Gerald Ford's Inauguration, 1974 August 9 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article - New York Times, by K. Brewster, 1974 August 11 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - SPEECHES
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1978, 1974 September 3 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Yale Law School Sesquicentennial Convocation Banquet, 1974 November 1 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Thanksgiving Message, 1974 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article: The New Journal, 1974 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - REPORTS
    - Report of the Committee on Freedom of Expression, 1975 January 8 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - SPEECHES
    - 100th Anniversary San Francisco's Childrens Hospital, 1975 February 4 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Regional Meeting Pine Manor, 1975 February 13 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - American Bar Foundation, Chicago, 1975 February 22 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Annual Dinner, The American Society of International Law, 1975 April 26 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - University of Michigan Commencement Address, 1975May 3 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - World Affairs Council of Northern California Asilomar Conference, 1975 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1975, 1975 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - College of William and Mary Commencement Address, 1975 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report of the President 1974-1975, 1975 July 28 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - SPEECHES
    - Freshman Assembly, Class of 1979, 1975 September 2 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Vanderbilt University Centennial Address, 1975 October 3 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Churchill Lecture, The English-Speaking Union of the Commonwealth, 1975 November 27 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - University of Oregon, Centennial Celebration, 1976January 16 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - CBS-TV Commentaries by Brewster and Letters Requesting Transcripts of Commentaries, 1975 February-1976 Ma (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1976, 1976 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - ARTICLES
    - Article: Los Angeles Times, 1976 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Article: London Daily Telegraph, 1976 July 4 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - REPORTS
    - Annual Report of the President 1975-1976, 1976 September 1 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - SPEECHES
    - Freshman Address, Class of 1980, 1976 September 7 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Opening Convocation, School of Organization and Management (Yale), 1976 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - 39th Judicial Conference, Philadelphia, PA, 1976September 20 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - REPORTS
    - Yale College Executive Committee Report on Academic Dishonesty, 1976 October 6 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - SPECHES
    - Cancer Center Groundbreaking, 1976 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - 275th Birthday (Yale), 1976 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - National Council on Philanthropy, 1976 December 1 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - New York County Lawyers' Association, 1976 December 9 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - The Meiklejohn Lecture: Brown University, 1977 April 18 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - SPEECHES & ARTICLES
    - Baccalaureate Address, Class of 1977, 1977 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Article: Yale Alumni Magazine and Journal (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - ARTICLES
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1977 June (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - SPEECHES
    - Freshman Address (Mrs. Gray), Class of 1981, 1977September 6 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - BACKGROUND AND BIOGRAPHICAL INFORMATION
    - Biographical Information, Official Biography, Circa1977 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Article: New Haven Register, Resignation: U.S. Ambassador to Great Britain, 1981 March 1 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Early Speeches and Articles, Biographical Information, 1941-1964 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - News Clippings, Press Releases, 1959-1978 (Box 6, Folder 150-152)
    - Articles, Clippings, 1961-1979 (Box 6, Folder 153-154)
    - Election: 17th President of Yale, 1963 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Article: Yale Alumni Magazine, 1963 November (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Statements, 1963-1968 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Mary Louise Brewster, Biographical Information, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Annual Reports, 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - MISCELLANEOUS
    - Associated Press Interview, undated (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - Untitled speech, title page missing, undated (Box 6, Folder 161)
- Material collected on Kingman Brewster, Jr., 1964-1988; Accession 1995-A-083
  - Articles, interviews, reports, 1964-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Awards, speeches, lectures, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biographical information, family, 1965-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Death, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Honorary degrees, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Obituaries, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Return to the United States; Class of 1941 40th reunion; return to Great Britain, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Television interview transcripts, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Speeches of Howard Lamar, 1992-1993; Accession 2000-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2029
  - Howard R. Lamar Personal Files
    - American National Biography, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - The Club, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Congratulatory Letters - No Reply, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Congratulatory Letters, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Delta Queen Trip, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Faculty Advisers, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Honorary Degrees - Personal, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Howard R. Lamar Fanfare/Commencement Day, May 24, 1993 (Box 1)
    - The Lamar Heritage, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Howard R. Lamar - Personal, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Howard R. Lamar - Roast, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - The Library of America - Board of Directors, 1993-1994, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Monroe Papers Advisory Board, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Mory's Cup Award Dinner, May 4, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Photographs - Art Gallery Pose, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Photographs (5x7) Favorite Choice from Proofs, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Howard R. Lamar (Scrapbook), 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Readers Encyclopedia of the American West, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Social Science Club, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Social Science Club Research Council, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Western Barbecue, June 26, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Western History Prize Association, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Western History Association, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale's Twenty-First President, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Howard R. Lamar Speeches, 1992-1993
    - Corporation Dinner, June 25,1993 (Box 1)
    - Dinner for the Officers, June 9, 1993 (Box 1)
    - School of Nursing Reunion, June 4, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Center for Jewish Life, May 30, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Education at Yale Panelists, May 30, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Reunion Classes, May 28, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Honorary Degree Dinner Toast, May 23, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Baccalaureate Address, May 23, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting/Donald Engelman, May21, 1993 (Box 1)
    - High School Honors Dinner, May 19, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Publication of Mark McCarren's "The Scientific Contribution of Othniel C. Marsh", May 19, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Sterling Scholars-Elm/Ivy Lunch, May 17, 1993 (Box 1)
    - John Hersey Memorial Service, May 15, 1993 (Box 1)
    - ALumni Association of Bergen County and Vicinity, May 13, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale Alumni Association of the Northwest, May 10, 1993 (Box 1)
    - 100th Anniversary of the Movies, May7,1993 (Box 1)
    - Harvard-Yale-Princeton-Dartmouth, May 2, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Richard Manoogian Luncheon, April 30, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Graduate School-Department of Psychology Reunion, April 30,1993 (Box 1)
    - William Warner Field Memorial Service, April 24, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Long Service Awards, April 21, 1993 (Box 1)
    - "Keeping the Faith"/Martin Ridge, April 14, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Gimbel Cup Presentation, April 8, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Community Service Dinner, March 30, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale College Council Forum, March 29, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Involvement by University in New Haven Economic Afairs, March 29, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Silliman Lectures-D. Allan Bromley, March 23, 1993 (Box 1)
    - David McCullough Inaugural-Hersey Lecture, March22, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Henry R. Luce Hall-Ground Breaking Ceremonies, March 11, 1993 (Box 1)
    - 150th Anniversary - Crew, February 27, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Dick Brodhead Dinner, February 21, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Moscow State University Visitors, February 17, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Inaugural Dinner, Friends of South Asian Studies Committee, February 17, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Early Action Days Parents Reception, February 15, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Perspectives as President - Yale Women's Center "Femininitea", February 12, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Walter Cronkite Dinner and Yale Medallion Presentation, February 11, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Divinity School Convocation, February 10, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale Comes to Chicago, February 9, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Facilities Planning, February 8, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Tulsa Speech, February 5, 1993 (Box 1)
    - The University and the City - New Approaches, February 1, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale Alumni Fund Board, January 25, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Houston Alunmi, January 21, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Dallas-Fort Worth-Alumni/Friends, January 20, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute, December 17, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Remarks at Dinner for J. Streets, December 15, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Luncheon - Cleanth Brooks, December 8, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Microsoft Day, December 8, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Fortunoff Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies- 10th Anniversary, December 7, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Fighting Back Panel, December 3, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Smilow Field Center, November 30, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Yale Club of Boston, November 20, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Art Gallery Governing Board, Yale, November 12, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Davenport College Master's Tea, November 10, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Yale Alumni/Friends in Pittsburgh, November 4, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Reception for Volunteers/Prospects, October 28, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Yale Alumni Association of Maryland, October 28, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Introducing Roberto Goizueta, October 27, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Alumni Fund Chairman's Award, October 23, 1992 (Box 1)
    - AYA Assembly XLI, October 23, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Yale Campaign Volunteer Luncheon, October 23, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Italian American Poetry Conference, October 12, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Installation- Reverend Streets, October 4, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Environmental Writers Conference, October2,1992 (Box 1)
    - Yale Round Table-Education at Yale in the Coming Century, September 30, 1992 (Box 1)
    - The Yale Campaign Volunteer Luncheon, October 23, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Dinner - Joan and Joel Smilow, September 23, 1992 (Box 1)